Selective colleges and universities in the U.S. are under fire for being too elite and too expensive, and for not training graduates for the world of work.
美国选拔严格的高校正受到抨击，被指过于精英化、收费过高，而且没有为职场培养毕业生。
Such charges ignore the fact that these institutions continue to prepare students for success in their work, for thoughtful engagement in civic life, for lifelong learning, and for understanding the world and those with whom they live.
这类指责忽视了一个事实：这些院校仍在帮助学生做好准备，让他们能在工作中取得成功、深思熟虑地参与公民生活、终身学习，并理解这个世界以及与自己共同生活的人。
These colleges and universities must be doing something right.
这些高校一定有做得对的地方。
Applications are at record highs, and their financial aid programs make them more accessible than ever.
申请数量创下历史新高，而这些高校的助学金项目也让学生比以往任何时候都更有机会就读这些学校。
This model of education has long played a central role in creating opportunity, driving economic growth, and spurring innovation.
长期以来，这种教育模式在创造机会、推动经济增长和激励创新方面一直发挥着核心作用。
Yet, there is growing skepticism about the value of this model.
然而，人们对这种模式的价值越来越怀疑。
The recent tax reform bill is a wake-up call that our strongest colleges and universities are under assault by some in government.
最近的税制改革法案敲响了警钟：我们实力最强的高校正遭到政府中一些人的攻击。
The initial proposals would have made education unaffordable for many by taxing tuition waivers for graduate students and ending deductions for student loan interest.
最初的提案要对研究生的学费减免征税，并取消学生贷款利息的税收扣除，这本会让许多人负担不起教育费用。
Thankfully, these provisions were ultimately stripped from the bill, but lawmakers let stand a new tax on the investment income of some colleges and universities.
所幸，这些条款最终从法案中删去了，但立法者保留了一项针对部分高校投资收益的新税。
While these attacks are motivated by misguided ideas, we need to do a better job of explaining why these claims are false and why what we do is valuable.
虽然这些攻击出于错误的观念，但我们需要更好地说明，为什么这些说法不实，为什么我们所做的事情有价值。
We cannot take for granted that any of this is obvious.
我们不能想当然地认为其中任何一点是显而易见的。
It is often said that elite colleges and universities do not train students, particularly those who study the liberal arts, for the workforce.
人们常说，精英高校没有为职场培养学生，尤其是学文科的学生。
But this can be refuted by scholarly research.
但学术研究可以驳斥这一说法。
The data are clear: a liberal arts education is great career preparation, both for excellent lifetime earnings and for satisfaction with the work.
数据清楚地表明：无论是要获得丰厚的终生收入，还是要对工作感到满意，文科教育都是极好的职业准备。
This education develops the skills of critical thinking, rigorous analysis of data and facts, communication with the written and spoken word, understanding of cultural differences and issues, and the ability to keep learning.
这种教育培养的是批判性思维、严谨分析数据和事实、以书面和口头形式交流、理解文化差异和文化问题的技能，以及持续学习的能力。
In fact, liberal arts graduates do extremely well in every imaginable field.
事实上，文科毕业生在能想到的每一个领域都表现得极为出色。
Access to an education at selective colleges and universities is now more available than ever to low- and middle-income families.
如今，中低收入家庭比以往任何时候都更容易获得在选拔严格的高校接受教育的机会。
We have built endowments from donations by alumni and parents who understand and appreciate our mission to provide access and opportunity, and a significant portion of the returns from these endowments is used to fund financial aid.
我们利用校友和家长的捐款建立了捐赠基金，这些捐赠者理解并赞赏我们提供入学途径和机会的使命；这些基金的收益中，有相当大一部分用来发放助学金。
Ironically, the new tax on endowments drains financial aid funds from the very schools most able to offer opportunity to those who have earned a spot but cannot otherwise afford this education.
讽刺的是，这项针对捐赠基金的新税，恰恰从这样一些学校抽走了助学金经费：它们最有能力为那些已赢得入学名额、但没有资助就负担不起这种教育的人提供机会。
Beyond the virtue of access to those who have earned a place at these schools, the diversity of economic backgrounds enhances the education and experience of all of our students.
让那些已赢得这些学校录取资格的人能够入学，这固然是一个好处；除此之外，经济背景的多样性还让我们全体学生的教育和体验都得到提升。